http://www.thefloorauthority.com/privacy_policy.htm

The Floor Authority Inc.
PRIVACY POLICY
The Floor Authority Flooring
Information Portal.
(TFAFIP.) is committed to maintaining the
privacy of personal information that you provide to us when using any of our
online services. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat the information we
receive when you transmit data to any machine owned by TFAFIP.
Web Form Information
When you submit information to TFAFIP. to make a payment or open an account, we
may collect personally identifiable information from you that may include your
name, address, email address, credit card number. We do not knowingly collect
personal information from persons under the age of eighteen.
Web Site Usage Information
We may automatically collect IP addresses and Web site usage information from you
when you access any of our online services. This information helps us evaluate
how our visitors and subscribers use and navigate our Web sites on an aggregate
basis, including but not limited to the number and frequency of visitors and
subscribers to each web page, and the length of their visits.
How We Use Information Collected
We may use information in the following ways:
For the purposes you specifically provided the information including, for
example, enabling us to process, validate and verify purchases.
To register you as a client and establish an account for you.
To send you email notifications about our new or existing
TFAFIP. products
and services, special offers, or to otherwise contact you.
To enhance existing features or develop new features, products and
services.
To provide advertisers and other third parties with aggregate information
about our user base and usage patterns.
To allow us to personalize the content and advertising that you and others
see based on personal characteristics or preferences.
Except as specifically set forth in this Privacy Policy, we will not share
your personally identifiable information outside of TFAFIP.
We may disclose and use personally identifiable information in special
circumstances where it is necessary to enforce our service agreements or terms
of use (for example protect our intellectual property rights). We may also
disclose or use your personal information when we, in good faith, believe that
the law may require us to do so.
Cookies
We define a cookie as any string of data that is automatically stored on your
computer upon access to our online services. TFAFIP. employs cookies to assign
temporary identification numbers to machines that access our web servers. This
information enables us to deliver faster service to our subscribers, prevent
denial of service attacks on our systems, detect and prevent fraudulent
transactions, and assist with awarding proper sales credit to our partners. All TFAFIP. cookies are 1) of limited duration, 2) less than 5KB in length, 3) only
visible to TFAFIP. web servers, and 4) devoid of any personally identifiable
information.
Security
The personally identifiable information we collect about you is stored in
limited access servers. We maintain safeguards to protect the security of these
servers and your personally identifiable information. We retain personally
identifiable information only as long as necessary to complete a purchase,
thwart fraud, provide customer service, or maintain your account with us.
Policy Modifications
We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post any changes
here, so be sure to check back periodically.
Comments and Questions
If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our Privacy Policy, you
may contact us at
* Note - Please remove red (  ) from address.
This policy was last updated 7 May 2004.
